https://www.parts-people.com/privacy.htm

Central Stardard Time Zone
Yes, We Are Open!
We remain open for business and all orders are shipping on-time daily (Mon-Fri)
--or--
Your Dell Service Tag is 7 characters long and is located on the bottom of your laptop or back of your computer. [Need Help?]
Finding LCD Screen Part Numbers and Specifications
Understanding the Different LCD Screen Backlight Types in Dell Laptops
Navigating support.dell.com to Find Your Laptop Specs and Part Numbers Using Your Service Tag
Does my laptop LCD screen need to be replaced?
$100 Diagnosis and Repair
Parts-People has been specializing in Dell laptops for 18 years. We are a leading supplier of Dell replacement parts and stock all laptop repair parts needed to repair your Dell laptop. We are a trusted supplier to 1000s of schools, government agencies, military and repair shops worldwide. Send your laptop to the Dell Experts!
Diagnose & Repair Info
How It Works
Laptop Repair Pricing
Dell DC Jack Repair
Part Installation Service
Send In Your Dell Laptop
Refurbished Laptops
About Our Company
About Parts-People.com, Inc
Nathan Morgan
Founder & CEO
Most of our orders are from repeat customers.
Parts-People began as a small company 18 years ago in an extra bedroom of my house. I had saved a small sum of money to purchase some computer parts and began selling them on eBay. After a few months I realized that people needed a place to go for Dell parts so I began building our website. Since we are located in Austin, Texas, where Dell.com was founded, I was able to set up a solid supply line with Dell. From the start, we focused on customer satisfaction and selling quality parts. We have grown a lot since 2002 but
still and always the customer will come first. You will find that we go above and beyond with every order and offer free resources and support before and after the sale.
18 years in business
over 2 million Dell parts sold
1 Year Warranty
Dell Genuine OEM Parts
Superior Customer Service
Safe Shopping Guarantee
We Are Reliable & Trusted
Dun & Bradstreet,
# 14-796-5961
clear text
Shop DIY Help Contact Us
Help Center
Search Help Topics
Browse Help Topics
Top Questions
Warranty & Return Policy
(www.parts-people.com).  This privacy
notice applies solely to information collected by this Parts-People.com.  It will notify you of the following:
1.
What
personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2.
What
choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3.   The
security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4.   How you can correct any inaccuracies in the
information.
How we collect and use (process) your personal information
Information
Collection, Use, and Sharing
Parts-People.com, Inc is the sole owner of the information collected on
www.parts-people.com. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily
give us via email, shopping checkout, or other direct contact from you.  We will not sell, rent, or share this information to anyone.
Contacting You
Parts-People.com
will use your information to respond to you,
regarding the reason you contacted us.
We will not share your information with any third party outside of our
organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship
an order.
Using This Website
In order to use this www.parts-people.com, as is true of most other websites, the Parts-People.com’s website
collects certain information automatically and stores it in log files.
The information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, the region
or general location where your computer or device is accessing the
internet, browser type, operating system and other usage information
about the use of the Parts-People.com’s website, including a history of the pages
you view. We use this information to help us design our site to better
suit our users’ needs. We may also use your IP address to help diagnose
problems with our server and to administer our website, analyze trends,
track visitor movements, and gather broad demographic information that
assists us in identifying visitor preferences. The Parts-People.com’s website also
uses cookies.
Website Registration and Purchasing
We request information from you on our checkout order form. To buy from us, you must
provide contact information (such as first name, last name, shipping address, billing address, phone number, and email address) and financial
information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is
used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble
processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you. We may also use your email information to inform you of changes to this privacy policy.
Credit Card Information
Parts-People.com does not store or save credit card information. Each time you place an order, you will be required to re-enter you credit card information.
Dell Service Tag
Parts-People.com will request Dell service tag information to help determine products compatible with your Dell PC. Parts-People.com will store this information in your website order to help Parts-People.com better offer support to you if needed in the future.
Your Access to and Control
Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any
time.  You can do the following at any
time by contacting us via the email address (info@parts-people.com) or phone number (866-816-5254) given on www.parts-people.com:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Cookies
“Cookies” are small data files that may be placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit the Parts-People.com site. Cookies permit the Parts-People's server to identify your browser whenever you interact with the Parts-People site. Parts-People uses cookies to improve the functionality of its site, to recognize repeat visits by users of its site, and to collect information about its users’ interactions with the Services. These Cookies contain identification information that enables us to streamline your experiences using the Services and the Parts-People site. These cookies may be placed by Parts-People or by select third party partners we collaborate with. To learn more or to opt out of placement of these cookies, visit the Network Advertising Initiative website or Digital Advertising Alliance website. You are always free to set your browser software to decline cookies. However, if you decline cookies, you will be required to reenter your login information each time you access the Services, and you may not be able to optimize the features of the Services. In some cases, you will not be able to access Services if cookies are disabled. By agreeing to accept cookies from Parts-People.com’s site, the following types of cookies could be placed on your computer.
Social Media Cookies: These cookies are used to integrate our site
with popular social media sites (Facebook, Twitter, etc.). Social Media
cookies allow visitors to share content quickly and easily with their
social networks
Analytics Cookies: These cookies are used to measure website traffic and activity
Advertising Cookies: These cookies help correlate online advertising
to a visitor’s interests by displaying marketing messages that are
relevant to a user based on a user’s browsing history and preferences.
Security
We take precautions to protect
your information.  When you submit
sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both
online and offline using 256bit TLS1.2 encryption.
Wherever we collect sensitive information
(such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to
us in a secure way.  You can verify
this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or
looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web
page. Credit Cards numbers entered on www.parts-people.com are not stored or saved.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive
information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline.
Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for
example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally
identifiable information.  The
computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are
kept in a secure environment.
Contact Us
If you feel that
we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately
via telephone at 512-339-1990 or via email info@parts-people.com.
Dun & Bradstreet,
About Parts-People | Dell Parts | Dell Repair | Parts People Coupon Codes | TOS & Policies | Contact Us
Not affiliated with Dell Computer Corporation
© Copyright 2002 - 2020 Parts-People.com, Inc. 2929 Longhorn Blvd #101, Austin, Texas 78758 All rights reserved | Privacy & Security
Parts-People.com, INC
This website uses cookies to improve your experience.
Accept Read Policy
